{
    "subject": "Fernando_Cerchio",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Lulu__1953_film_",
    "human_readable": "Fernando Cerchio directed the film Lulu (1953).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9580078721046448,
            "question": "Who directed the film Lulu in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8799096345901489,
            "question": "Fernando Cerchio is known for directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8390368223190308,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Fernando Cerchio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8084646463394165,
            "question": "Who directed the film Lulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050721883773804,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Fernando Cerchio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8047266006469727,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Fernando Cerchio."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7925615906715393,
            "question": "Which film was directed in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696550250053406,
            "question": "What film did Fernando Cerchio direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6137391924858093,
            "question": "What year was the film Lulu released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4777916967868805,
            "question": "In what year was Lulu released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fernando Cerchio directed the film Lulu (1953).",
            "html": "yago_17342_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Lulu released?",
            "html": "yago_17342_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Fernando Cerchio direct?",
            "html": "yago_17342_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which film was directed in 1953?",
            "html": "yago_17342_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17342_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe query asks if Fernando Cerchio directed the film Lulu (1953). In one of the provided context documents, it indeed states that there is a mention of an Italian \"Lulu\" filmed in 1953 by director Fernando Cerchio and starring Valentina Cortese and Marcello Mastroianni. This directly supports the query and confirms that the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Fernando Cerchio directed the film \"Lulu\" in 1953."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}